[Music]
or
hey dehli dehli kach peepdi ke
[Music] put aap khaali
musale
[Music] toh mundo kaam tu che pa
[Song voice] hey
re
[Music] hey pagli munni aa rahila
[Music] hey badhiyachi
toh bhi pada re [Music] hey what is this look who re
[Music]
[Music] hey
ko dhu ka
upar very soft soft la pale khi lo jungle bhi bhi egg pakko khab hey musa ko egg pak hai hey
egg dekhli and pee egg TV
dekhli kukunda very khang egg
sab
[Music]
eat ame seguda khab nahi chale basanti me jiba jaane
ask ki se egg o feather hey peacock hey peacock bhi se
mane o feather anda khantu ki kur
egg ko khantu a throat
[Music]
hey three ko re toh dehli
who re jungle pak do dhao
hey fool auto feather kept jungle saw
run
[Music]
Hey boy hey hey
you didn't even come
[Music] from
going
hey and Anna I mean Sanda Tanda ko Susangi
such a Tandava
Sanda Konda
ko you are not Sanda and
today
[Music]
hey who
sa [Music]
hey
[Music]
[Music] you have
destroyed the shoe [Music]
Papa Papa come out
Magaru come out give me
cucumber give me a stick
[Music]
hey sa then you hit my brother's throat who will do it
who will do it so the
egg a Musa [Music] do the
work of the nail give me the egg keep me at home also the
egg see the house when you
see
Musa
listen hey Prabhu ay then
also see
Prabhu
[Music]
or
hey Dholua saa hey everyone go out
[Music]
hey which mantra is being thrown
saala go
home go
[Music]
hey Baba the mudi is being fried all the mistakes oh hey
you are digging the
egg
video
this is the kitchen
fire ko aari [Music] fun fun  If you don't see the video list, please
subscribe to our channel as soon as possible,
thank you Dantu
[Music]